fontgarden.com 2006-12-17

# Privacy policy

**Privacy Statement for Font Garden**

**Font Garden - daily downloads of free fonts** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Font Garden.](http://www.fontgarden.com/index.html)

#### Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information. To view Extreme Trackings privacy policy go here: [http://www.extreme-dm.com/tracking/privpol.html](http://www.extreme-dm.com/tracking/privpol.html)

**Cookies**

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Font Garden uses Burst Medias advertising service - the privacy policy for Burst Media is outlined here: [http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp)

**Third Party Advertising**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

We use BUDS INC and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

#### Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

#### Order Forms 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

#### Contests 

We will eventually run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

#### External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Font Garden - daily downloads of free fonts** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us . 

  1. You can send email to [ellinor@fontgarden.com](http://www.fontgarden.org/fontshop/contact_us.php)
  2. You can visit the following URL: http://www.fontgarden.com/contact/contact.htm 

#### Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [ellinor@fontgarden.com](http://www.fontgarden.org/fontshop/contact_us.php)
  2. You can visit the following URL: http://www.fontgarden.com/contact/contact.htm

## Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
